About how depressing the
standing is, but he gave a fantastic talk on the
topic of negative thoughts,
and the entire morning was
dedicated to this topic.
I wanted to take a longer break, and
so today I'm going back to
this explanation of the structure of the aces
courses. If you want to become a loser, then
the structure of the 18 foundational courses should be in the back of your mind.
We've done four of them, and I'd like to
continue with that.
Maybe we'll do three or
four more courses. What is it? What are the
things we talked about in each course?
Tell me, whatever it is, a
field, the river, why does the course come
before,
and why does the course come after? Yes, where is
the positioning in this sequence of the
intersection courses? Because here are the five
churches' themes, and if there were four
schools, and then we should articulate the content.
That's something different that you know in some places. It's
not a great book.
Most of these courses have a
great commentary. I don't use
the ancient original poems with her.
All these evil poems need
an explanation. I've picked the best ones
for this, and I would
also say which ones.  Comments for each
course unite have firstly do this now
before I do this I
looked at a course and
thought
for me it is very interesting the
flow of the five great topics church
course which topic comes first
how do you go with your school and
yesterday to the highest school or until the
next school year in case you
die halfway this money course
maybe it is the ones that
start with the top and the selection just the
death rate is quite high 25 years it
much naturally my manager 61
young men started and four of them finished
and that is
quite typical for it is a lot of money
from one class finish and the
others left as
extinct or could not do it
recognize that means less than
ten percent
how do you see the order and that a
bit unexpected that needs
explanations okay and I have it in the
document in your manual under
thought some of the manual
documents are not finished yet if
the documents do not look finished
casually leave them not finished as well as
an attempt to do the whole thing in 33
training  To finish cycles at the
end of this year, you want all
the polis, the polis is the basic
things for, is for the whole
structure, and the first is the 75 pages of
text, text that is like choosing the
knowledge of Master St. dictated by one
's secretary who wrote the inner part,
he is, if you know the
dog story of the lion dance case,
then you know how that happened, five
great ones before these, the length of
the first five topics, perfection of
wisdom number four,
it is which school, the lower middle
school, we have also learned
the way is explained, I have, as
27 years, it is called this greatness, I have taught,
I have a way
understood the perfection of wisdom
not to explain, the writings of the
Middle Way are, is a
huge one, in civilian service, from all
Marianna Exter, all police about learning,
are there except the hidden
presentation, from ever since, all the answers
are incredibly similar to the one he, like back then, I have there once,
is all the
basics you need to know, hundreds of
Ideas
of the middle way, the choice of
realization soon,
written by the next brother, a pretty
good source than all agree that
they are relieved that he
is already relieved and only that
people collect enough to know him
well now and that
comes very, very close to this,
this flap, this
literature with which we spend twelve
years, the first twelve years,
functions are expanded, so the first thing you
learn, 75 pages of the learned and
wise of it, and 15, it is great, the
children or young in the twelve
coalition, right, and every night around
this time out onto the
terrace, and they, the experimenters, to
pigs, as the children of other houses
want, the whole monastery of the 15-year-olds
in Switzerland, this text, but it is
a custom, then the turning point needs
something recited, then you should make it loud enough
so that the spirits in the
room, glorious tradition, that not to the
name, but please say it quite well
and loudly, so what all the spirits
in the room that Lord can instead, I
found that  It's already clear that after
twelve years we're doing this,
which is logical. After that, let them perfect their
understanding of Heydt,
and then bring back
the many years of material.
Mittelberg, that's 13 to 16 of the
church course for four years, basically a
deal. He gives lectures to perfect,
technically speaking, you have something in
sunny weather. There,
a great comment marked the commitment,
the wisdom, and these books have
connected classic textbooks. The
commentaries we use are
huge
for the first twelve years, the 2000
pages of commentaries from one car.
That means each monastery has its own most
monastery commentaries. Normally, there are
two differences.
Trittin said some things. Then it means the
entirety of our means
because of and particles. Germany means
analysis, and at the church together,
it will be written in an innovative style,
always between those that
collide with each other. So we do
n't learn the first twelve years. We learn
on eight huge stages of
our lot that we come for the second time.
The middle way is that I would
spend time with ways and
then again there are the animals, but that
exists in German, there is an
overview
and there is an end to the area, they are
incredibly beautiful books,
we should also translate them sometime,
in that time they have incredibly beautiful
books and there are commentaries for
each of these books and we use
for the middle way,
also 26 books, what do you think
we use
for the body, for the body, a good student, the diocese of the
hardcore students, then
she not only lets the two months have passed since that
in 2010,
but you will also get to the body,
section, body's explanation, she has thus
explained the rangers 10, if
enlightenment,
those were thoughts, Madonna and I
attacked, really meant that this
happened in our translation services,
knew what was going on, we are just
halfway through, it took 5 years,
750 say so far about 1500-2000,
we should be finished with that, that
is, body's ultimate comment,
mostly not enough time to now a
cartel  To learn 30 on this topic, I
came across
special lectures from a super,
spent 8 years on it, yes, started with four or
five of my friends, they
all gave up,
for me it was cool, no, I had an
hour with the greatest master of
seriousness, could spend it, it was
incredible, that was the one, by now
we spent two years together,
numbers 17 and 18 are
the topic, like the beloved happening of
morality, active in Vienna, so that the main
book, that is not written by any super
but by people,
every monastery,
comments and if you have an interest in it, I
like to talk, I know it's maybe
boring, I ca
n't talk about it,
usually a bonbon means
a summary of the whole thing as a
poem and you memorize
everything that is now one of these, she knows
now the shortest possible and a
comment on it,
but normally they are a bit longer,
she knows it by heart, really, really
want to go into the depths, then there are
incredible comments, King Smith gave
me a lottery win in his, these
are smaller, not so famous authors,
but such a comment is the best and
I have started on this  Occupied pots
worked on it for five years,
then the person gave up and went to
Algiers. The common belief would
not only be right, but what to do
because the monks
did not live 250 100 253 full beloved
for a 9 370. They spend 17
years in the monastery before they learned to love,
and that leads to another detail:
the cash courses that I should mention,
and that is the role because it is
against the Romans, because it is against or one
number of poor area means the
house teacher of the quality of such a kind
of visit is from the children. They
look after the children. The monastery
started, we were all
refugees. All the children
were in the room, and they all were
then in companies, and the
children begin, and the customers go on. Above all, they had
these large open wounds
on their bodies.
It is to enjoy food,
and from the housemother's house, it was
probably 509.
It is a task to feed them and
find the money for it and give them
clothes.  to give and here this is a
task to see them to like will
normally be these people who, in
addition to the church course, will be the ones we will
soon praise through personal
experience,
and so you get to know your beloved in the
monastery. They might not
sit with you and bring it along when he
did that.
He used a Tibetan commentary
that is called that, too close
to his audience.
He then
wrote 2000 to the beloved. Many monks and
nuns wrote incredible forms to the body and
want a different tradition. Parents
Katja, that's an incredible commentary
that they used. I still use it almost every
day when I see my teacher.
That's incredible. This commentary
and this commentary follow. I got the one
in my beloved that as soon as
I recently turned 30. I
was lucky because I didn't have to do
all the bad things before today.
I did everything you
can imagine, really. I think it
's maybe in old age that you do
n't know each other for a month up to 30 years,
and if I go to  30 insanely
the following beloved taken
they learned before they
became a full monk
it was possibly even want not to
observe any longer
it was a great honor if possible to
become and so often was would because it
is so to later my life
has made the answer or question is before the
17 years of the church choir reached
your house empty all beloved taught
by telling what you are not
and may then through and in
this organic in this organic way
learn all the young
monks beloved for example I am
not allowed to take my rom
I may let go
and we
climb over it that is against beloved Lucy
find out that you can take my head or
undress and I may not go over the
top I think there are very many
rules and you can't write that in my
book when the teachers
beat rosary then you can remember understand
that is the
Viennese then you can after 17 years
you can the ancient stories and
guides here is something in the joint is the
original causes we are completely  A very
important idea in the domestic
organization, for example, looks like
your places, or it's long since meant
someone made a mistake,
for example, originally, as
Buddhists, it was allowed to drink alcohol, there's
the buddy Gaal to learn, we were
allowed without drinking, then a
long period was given, problems arose,
I can't remember what
it was,
but you can learn that, that's why you can
search for a long time, besides alcohol, and you'll
find within a million
pages, personnel, within ten seconds,
I could have found you, now the writing with safety
goggles, database, you let me
now ask what was the cause, what was
the incident that was traced back, I
know that within ten seconds,
find the courses, find the one that
gets it, this one is bigger, the
information is even more accurate because I
checked everything in the database,
access to thousands of books, 10,000,
and therefore I can check things right away,
okay?
[Music]
I like to tell stories,
maybe you've already
noticed, I was on a plane one day,
a contract from a lama, to hear, to
say many  People on the plane I did
n't know, who were in the same
city, warned to hear this person.
I translated there once during this
period. I have twelve years of experience translating with
consumers again.
I worked there once and
came to the point where it steers here
for alcohol. He said I have such a
simple story, and the Wittlicher one
is that we sat there and we found each other, and
then beer is
ordered. I was surprised. Then I thought up a
good
plan. I found the page
where the mother's brother says, "
I drink so much alcohol that it
fits on a blade of grass, a drop."
He says, "Don't think it, then
I won't call a Buddhist, namely, no
longer a student. You are no longer a student. You are
then a person. I like you, but
if you are no longer a student,
I found the page. Did you
help me with it? It's the same.
I can't really imagine it. Of
course,
this is lived experience. The morals happen, and
between 19 and 20, like rapid
amateurs, who again, like me, except
when they are in others.  Schools appear
for 18 years, 1920, make a year
again, information is allowed there at
their lectures and always comes back. In
everything, she is in the first 18
years, you get a big one, it's like back then
but in the year 1920, you learn, I was
formally in it back then, in addition, there are
usually fewer than ten
Munich classes left and it's kind of strange
because you know what the others
know and you know that you can't
read,
therefore there can be no more debate,
the debate is very boring. You
are 18 years old with the psychological one
and realize that he was never the
four. The four work,
state that you get the last year,
they do something cool in the monastery, they
bring two classes together, to ticket
is currently, they bring the next
class to the next class,
skips if a year, which is
unfortunate, my class has, we
were the, our class, we
actually skipped because there was only more,
produced, but 5
fractions and they left out the two classes.
I am norms in the law,
so to speak, we went back a few
Years spent on it,
but most people, and not
always, have holes in their
training because of what happened in the monastery.
We did
n't really cover that topic properly.
It's so important that it doesn't
just solve the problem; it's the key to the majority emptying the door.
It's so important that every year for three
months you stop everything. The whole
monastery has gentlemen on all classes,
and you go to a special group and
you learn the topic again. Topic
number three is the second school, so
dreary, especially from the book.
I always don't do that because I do
n't want us to make that mistake.
I don't want him to shame me with
someone. I want the announcement to be a
great success. Last night, the rain had a chance to be
live from Singapore.
She was loving enough that she had a
fantastic good Maputo, where that is, where she
equips herself with hot spices and
God. But can I get something that I had
before it
was mixed with the chocolate cake? The
best car I've ever made.
You can always do it.  If you want to come to my
house, I'll pay you to
come to me. I have money from Word,
and it would be fantastic. And after that,
we had something with the chocolate Kuhn
from not, and I'm happy to report that
I checked. I took one of these, which
I didn't
exactly hand over. Kerbs, than ever watched. I
think that's why they got me so far.
I don't know how many
might have experienced this,
but it was a very good
lesson.
If we died in Greece,
we think that he told this
story with the cake that tasted good, that's why
people
say for ten years that things don't stick with
me. I don't always remember that you can
repeat it, or you can force an
importer of cake with chocolate
to eat it and connect this bad
memory with a bad one.
That's much, much more powerful.
People don't forget that. Every time
you can have a drink, your
players can do something interesting.
What is your job as a teacher? I don't know.
I don't know the culture.
I don't know anything about
Finland except that it starts with many
and the country has its own food.
For me, things that
tasted bad make it so that your
faster eating,
make your own. We once did
a retreat and we
made a plan: yes, everyone had a big,
heavy dinner with lots of gravy. Then
we gave the meditation right after the
meal and everyone fell asleep,
and everyone was
unhappy. Then we said that
we did that intentionally and to show
them that they should
n't eat that food before meditating, that they shouldn't
eat before meditating. And
they were guaranteed to do that to us again,
but they didn't forget it.
21 to 24, the church warned shortly before 20
years ago on the 25th.
Here, 21 to 25, if you
decide for a higher guest,
then you wait to be checked. In addition,
then not for a
bigger one, the one who wants to have it,
maybe has to wait a few years, but there is
a clinic, how many games can be played,
two normal and two advanced
church each year.
There is a bottleneck, as before, they
stay, they wait until someone dies and
then the next one is excluded,
that up to ten years waiting
if you want the highest church because you are the
Highest church,
you must be debated at Easter,
all seven major political issues from now,
from 10.2 years ago, 2002, and then
that I was beaten, that in
seven great colleges, and you
must seem for every politician,
I almost came to LTA, but I didn't have to
go to all the political ones,
then you get him down, that
shouldn't waste your time,
and then you would carry, for
example, studies clarify,
but then it has what it really meant, that's
a daily or specialized learning,
we learn that there is a very
important thing, is there another topic
that I would like to live in, says back,
those are next to number four,
okay, okay, that's what they say, yes, the
choices of knowledge and they form,
he mentions the twelve dependencies and
the wheel of life, in ten,
and that's it, there is, so that
you need to take this cell out
and write a whole book about this whole cell,
it's called back and prepares the
extraction and from a juice of a
plant and to obtain medicine, is the
process of pressing, blowing out,
sufficient controls and  Then in the
end you get the juice out of the plant
and in the end you use it, saying
that medicine gets the juice out of the bed
and then my separate contract,
great game, seriously, and my
great school, one of these appointments is
one of them, ultimately Samsung, that
's so disgusting and parts of the
standstill, one of them is
dependent, stand the  Twelve songs of the
dependent mood, one of them
means all possible combinations
of the five plaintiffs. There are 20 possible ways,
assumed Kristina Jana Fix, the
founder's move to another room. There are
20,420 places, the 20-year-old calls herself.
My video can come to enlightenment in
different ways. Gold price, that
these books were missing, our monastery, values,
cultural revolution, all
burned, all copies spent, and they
had the thieves here no longer, they were
missing. Such a devout project
found him in Russia,
revived him, she gave one, and that
was the first thing ever printed
on a computer at the request. That was
in the year 22 meters, and in this set, he is
proud of it anyway. If it connects, has made
a story, or
destroyed for 30 years at ten million euros
because they were far, and they still did it
with me. If so, then immediately
the most private ones, his bottles, there are
many people in a class who have
n't died, then you
pause as an urgent interpretation.  Here,
this is done every year in
winter for three months. You
logically do school number two because it's
so important for every topic. It's
incredible for every team.
Then, there's a custom in Tibet. It's
really cool. Every year for a
month, the wild, the monastery where
the 50 best candidates from
50 to 80 students go. That's your team. You're
with him. They get
a backpack, a
sleeping bag, and a blanket, and they
go to his monastery. The ancestors... It's
a special monastery, a
small monastery in Bergen. Then
they debate there together for a month. You
mean all day,
once a week, twice a
week, guests... They sleep through the whole night,
debate all
night, and it's like the Olympic
Games in their monastery. 300 stops and as
well as learning...
Two months of preparation for the
winter debate. You go somewhere...
And the children weren't so good...
They stay home and they try
the next one.  to get better this year and
then they can
participate again, that's why I'm going to be clean. It's very, very
rare to go to a debate
or two. I'm too much,
I'm leaving. Why? I said I'm leaving right now,
whether you want me out
or not.
I still know what I can do. He said the way
the dark effect works. I'll do it.
I was the 51st. He's a member and
I'm so glad I did it
because then I understood.
I've had great breakthroughs on
this topic. I learned in the fall that I listened
extremely to course reactions.
I lost half of my students,
and when I learned that,
I lost half of all the students.
I stopped in 80, 40 years.
It's really difficult for me.
I decided I'll do it. I can do it.
Something to you and I'll get the house. Don't be
afraid. I have no
attempts to tackle the difficult topics. Into
the coalition from Zug
and I've become the best because
I simply... I remember that I was
so annoyed and had a footstep.
Then you just do it. Okay, understand. Yes,
that is...  These are the seasons, saviors, women,
so much time, maybe
nothing today, the class, gentlemen, I would like to
discuss what's going on, can
the camera work,
one assumes why, that was one of my
motivations, what a motivation, these are
the 18 basic course, I
have mine as a Westerner, one lets the
Western person, yes, we didn't grow up with
the idea of ​​chambers, grew up in
China, every
different country has at least
the word chamber, at least people talk about it a
little, maybe how
much of it is wrong and superficial,
that is at least heard in
Western culture because I did the course
for Western people, most
Americans and Europeans, almost
South Americans, but I thought I
should do a course about came, so here
strong, the parts of cannabis steadily
opened in the USA, when I was
growing up, I don't remember
my mother telling me, I can, the
first time I heard that this will be a topic,
and in the years 1854, 1950s,
in the 50s, which was very, very, he, the
word came, to stop,
but  My mother, I don't know, I didn't save
any clubs at the house,
flying with a newspaper.
My mother said, "Bring me
flying, don't do that." Why? You can have very
bad karma. Is there anything? Is
bad karma? It comes back to you,
and how? Why? Does the level stay where it goes? Where would there be
none? It's not easy.
The camera,
now I ask so many questions.
That was the understanding of most,
but no one on the topic of chambers has opened up. We do
n't know where it goes, the seed,
not my people. That's why they say a
giant boomerang. Whoever goes to Mars
and then comes back,
we all have this strange
idea now on the topic of karma. There are
so many strange ideas on the topic. Did
he come to my country, my culture, that we should
learn that again.
As I mentioned before, it's
also a country where people
always talk about chambers.
Unfortunately, you can't understand. They simply believe it
just because the mother said that
we will ever come to an important phase,
and mine took it, talking about it all
night. It's simple, Lindt,
what to do, the seams have done
that.  There are religious reasons why I
gave the course in the chambers at that time, because none of the
students had learned chamber. He learned.
I am very proud of this course.
If you, how can one work? There are
all the details on the topic. I came to the
church with it, and we use very
intensively. Beautiful Lammers commentary, also
the commentaries of the first palace. The first
Dalai Lama wrote a good commentary on
the topic. He was a young
man. He is now at the Cape. An old man of
all men, that will be a few years. You
have many questions about this, but with
your pictures for the 18 basic course,
the summary for the recommendation is
needed. But I have the word. That is
a designation. I found a drawing
of him from that day. Take it,
but it certainly had to
happen the next day.
One would have had a whiff of Canon. Who
that is is very specific. So it allows it
here to have no hair, but it
looks like it's not down here.
We are trying to find the picture for you.
This calming is the best first
biography to draw and body.  In the
world, 1000 readers. If you want to know more about your
own tradition, then let it be
fun. It's entertaining. It
's big. Yes, there are many pictures. This
happens. 15 famous painters. 1. It took
15 years and the theme
is finished.
If you really want to, they want to
eat something on campus. Then I tell
people, make it a coffee table
book in his living room.
Every time someone comes,
just open the book. There is a great
tradition in the monastery that we open the book
on a holiday or birthday. On Sunday, there will
soon be something on Sunday. It should have been in
the 80s. Question: Why does it
recognize that this book is also open today on Sunday?
But this is a message from around
and from the cutter. Thirtieth tradition.
Have you found the game? The team
drew the picture again.
The Lavadom Sony's Kentrup courses. What sex?
Yes, what is it? Someone not only that to the
day and you know that right, this has
an interesting story in the
background. This is fitting stories
to tell, like I
wrote this one recently.  I was
in 17 in a monastery where
you meet someone, so it's not
all cool, it's a huge... I
think it's a shame,
I think it's a shame that
most guests don't have it anymore, that
the people of Manching didn't learn it,
they don't know all of this in detail,
and I think I
told the story... we lived in a
Mongolian
community in a temple with
50 people, most of them...
we managed it... I then
meant we go to the houses, there's
no other place, left side...
I said it was the first day, then it happened,
but we take them... a
comment... the lady should demand... so far
it's not that easy, not...
but it's done... I wrote a
dictionary about it... back then that took
ten years... when
they drove closer to the hospital, I
canceled four because when I said...
namely, go... that sleep has to be as usual...
and then I... for
the community... first... formed...
then they give you... for lunch...
sometimes... and  Monks live,
you get a small red one, everyone signs,
I know all the communities, would that be
exciting,
many think that they get money or a
good lunch, and we are all
together, that should be the deficit in
Mongolia, which one is sure that you
respect that extraordinarily highly, that
the market in China and Japan, Vietnam is
also respected, that the man
recites himself, even ten points, and blind
church from the script of Kolya, and he
learned the car, that the family
died with a pillow in their mouth, we
were together, it becomes a policy,
taken in the mouth and said, you can
really be surprised to
get such a difficult carp out of your hand, didn't eat, but
loved that, so it is, let's open the
writings, because he gets for that, would have applications,
quickly censor lunch,
and she said yes, but not the same,
simply open, and everyone
comes differently, rarely that I
quote to it, but then he hit,
you understand what, the family does
n't understand that,
and the person said that doesn't matter,
how understandable
solar power goes,
I have to learn that, we have  In Russia,
big things that we wrote the Vedic
commentary on, it's a long one,
if we welcome it, she got a
taste today from Lammers
Tel.
He is a great writer.
We found I'm going there, we have
cameras coming there, ported, which is also
Salon 2010, coming soon, from that,
the waterways, yes, always something
interesting can happen,
I spent many hours sitting there
and I didn't have much,
the middle one, there is a course, what is the
next thing, what some next, that the
supposed gate, do
n't come out of the question today, answer,
and then I emphasized that the
translators in the hospital, therefore it would
n't be that, I know myself in the soup,
always memories, and then we did
this course,
if you ask what the river is, then
you either say lunch or the
hospital,
those are the two rivers, or the
master, a good story again,
student, church decided that
he, before every Muslim, understandable, before
one continues with the course, that is
a good man, is also a good
reason, photo  Too soft in the basic
course, I explained it so that you get a
good dose, understand, but had a
higher average, yes, the first course,
but not in another course.
You haven't yet clarified a course on the
topic of majority,
we always know two,
but it's our means,
one may assume, will also find a middle ground, it's
good if it's a good
instrument, so you have that, that's the
logic of course number 6. I'm still trying to do it
now, and then practice
now, and
most of you probably know that
14 years,
that tells me that the Russian
Academy of Sciences, 14 years,
then only a catalog has been made,
the books haven't been put in yet,
we've still done that,
and hopefully, if we can get our friends
there someday,
that's at least a scanning, there are
many books, read aloud,
try to save them, Jens, in some
form, where is my life, is that also not, would have,
and I have them today,
today has moved him forward, or things happen,
fire happens,
we have received permission
to be a ruling monastery, and when we
digitize and catalog, we
every  The image in each book,
tens of thousands of mitigates, these are
cataloged. There is one very
special one; they have been searching for a long time. There is
a single, unique
print in the world. Do
you have this? It can be found. This is also
Lama. I was pleased, so a little bit, it's
simply gone. What this
course has been, in part, is the book
sold? There are already 35.
I think it's interesting. This is
bigger. It was started in the book,
and I am polite.
This is Krupp's maxim: no pressure.
Beloved, the beloved of the Federal Council.
I tried to find much of it.
This is somewhat difficult, but I managed to find
the Castor. Scroll down for a
lifetime.
[Music]
That was really for many of the
police. Although it was successful, they recorded it.
We also have beloveds from, according to, Buda
and other sources. And in this course,
I have the DB AG or four sources for
the 64 beloved of a priest.
Chinese friends, who
recently asked me about their first beloved, certainly
not to teach him about this beloved.
If I have everything from this tradition, it has
come to China in this form
and  Therefore, it is good that these 64 64
total how many root beloved 18
46 a second beloved and many others
but there is the point from to the body
the highway 4 it became something that loved
me
he explained wrong every beloved
recommend if this summary was
the most important summaries Tibet
printed then this book always comes
first there must be a reason
for it
the car boom believe this book
none of which there is an incredible
Bavarian church the chain through an email
from a church of a much weaker
monastery Beverungen you must be
loyal to your monastery
but he was the teacher one day he said
that a book of writing
now say cathedral and the ministry
and means 33 are from cliffs 41 the
freedom beloved Munich but the
human being then you write then there are
253 detach how you must explain
this this church
he decided that a book
about all three groups
he decided that he would make it slowly
and  6 he made
leaves what is the core of the beloved
completely and very briefly and everyone goes
that there is in three or four sentences has
decided
all loved including the tantric
beloved that are hundreds of polyps
the great book written
this book very correctly very precisely
played said that Sonja what to put
whether it is here on your mountain scholar
and has entered a three-year and in the
mornings I have the people
that was a very very neat lecture
and while it has been overshadowed by others
and this this
contract incredibly important if your
especially if you want to become a nun
you should learn this is
extraordinarily important says yes important
experience
that is yes happy with that we have
found half of his book
found half of the pages spent a million
years trying to
find them seemed Smith helped us
we found the pages in many
countries we found all the pages have
here 30
therefore we should the screen world
mean
[Applause]
[Music]
what should we do however motto
which school is this yes he loved
that are audible middle way another
course then  Let's go,
hopefully we'll go to the class around Menowin at the
monastery, and my point means I
hope so, is that it? Because it means
Klostermann, sometimes, if we want to, but
maybe not. We'll come back, don't worry.
This, by the way, refers to
8 death and the areas of life, that one of the most
positive courses everyone came to,
and then I said they asked me
what the next course is. Someone
says someone dies and you go, what
are the possibilities after you die,
what are the places you
can land? A friend of mine will probably die
tonight, and it's good
to know where you can land. It's good to get ready to die,
and it's
a book about how to
prepare for death. The
background to this is when I put the
courses together
when I did the course, because
it was very popular there.
It's a very exotic, very sexy book,
and a friend of mine ends up in a
psychiatric hospital after reading it
because he read it without a teacher, and
he was really in a
psychiatric
hospital for over a year, and interestingly...  Is this
simply wrong?
The Tibetan Book of the Dead is wrong; it
's not authentic and not accurate.
It lacks the fundamental quality. If you believe
Barack Obama studied it and consulted
other authentic sources,
it's not as described there.
Please tell people
that this book is incorrect.
We don't study it, we do
n't use it; we used
other sources back then. That's why
I thought it would be good to have a
truly accurate description of what
happens to the dead and what the
possibilities are. After the dead go,
the
future lives are proven in Course
4.
And then you wonder, do people choose the
lamps in my future
life and other paths? Again, I come
from a culture that doesn't believe in future
lives. First, future
lives have to be explained, and then
I have to
say where they go, what
those 49 days were about, and what the
spirit world is. That's why
I decided to write this course.
After you know that
future lives exist, you
also have to give information on how to get
there. This course was created by
my mother.  Inspired because when I
first studied Buddhism in Asia,
my mother got cancer and died,
and then I
asked my lover what I should do now,
my mother is going to die, and so
I said my mother wasn't
Buddhist, and that didn't
interest her, and I wrote from India. There was
no email back then, so it took
two or three weeks.
Sometimes I received letters from
her a year later.
I wrote to her, "Come, what do
you have to lose?" They
fired her; she was already a teacher, she was
in the class, and
then they fired her because they said
the children would freak out if they
saw you having a seizure. And then I got a promise, "
What do you have to lose?" And then she
came, and she had never been outside
the United States, and she was very
sick.
We took her to the library; she lay
in the back seat. She was
very sick, and then we leaned her against
the wall during the lectures, and
I think for three times three months
they taught her how to die properly.
That's to  The right cabbage, and this
should be a course for everyone, and
this course came from my
personal experience because I thought
people should have a complete
description of what happens when you
die. I like this course;
we use the Abi lady and gladly jobs.
Comment on this:
Tim, the next picture please, man there. I
will change his name to Tim, man, and other.
Now we continue.
I also used the book center Tempo.
The biggest book in Tibet is Lan.  G of
chips and katar in English will be
that 10,000 approximately 8,000 times if
we were to translate it with
footnotes and he took exact measurements from
an earlier book written
the big book about the stages of the day
November is called the big book about the
teachings and he stole the title and
also the content of
the prototype was that the first, the
first prototype, cadaver times of 1000
and it is the longest book that could have been
written, a text helps,
his text is about ten pages
and that is very typical for the charter for
the Caramba poems and that is the
master book of the campus and it is a
complete lamp, the complete
Buddhism, very difficult to read, old
400 years, presentable, and we
have it, it was disappeared in the world
after the Cultural Revolution, how could
not find it,
tennis helped me,
I think interest must have been chips
many years ago and we found it together,
we have half a book in Russia
of obituaries  We found a few pieces,
I think in Indonesia, and then
we put them together and
created a new edition. We
printed it at the monastery.
We saved the book, and when I
wrote it over cappuccino, there's
a story about the
body sitting with his students. He
said, "I wish we could
find the lost book because
it sounds really good." And they
searched for it, and we found it.
He found the only copy from that
time, 400 years after it was
written. And here's the picture of
him,
very excited. Normally, you
use a whole bundle of incense sticks,
not just one, but 30
or so.
And when an Obama comes, everyone has
a silk scarf or a flower.
He understands what I'm saying.
With the red envelope in his other
hand, you greet a high lama
with incense sticks, a silk scarf,
and a donation.
And in the picture, you can see how
the book is handed to the body,
and he does the same as a
high lama.  The lama has the incense sticks in his
hand and is wearing a silk scarf. He's trading
the book like a high lama, and that's
depicted in the picture.
And I believe it is,
and that's why I thought it was very, very
promising to include a bit of the
book in course 8.
Part of the course is from this book.
Three years ago, we had a high
lama send us a package. Someone
told me it was rare, and
inside was the pamphlet I printed 20 years ago.
Thank you.